The blad image cannot be displayed. The file has have been moved, received, or ablack Vario that the link points or the served file and bospool.

# Esprit Hodge

Customer Service/Admin

My name is Esprit Hodge, I am 26 year old AAS Graduate of Portland, OR. I have a lot of experience and have worked in very important positions. I'm looking to expand my knowledge and work hard to support myself and my family. I moved to Texas for family and because, I know of the great reputation of good jobs. I do have some knowledge in Spanish. I write and read it much better than I speak it. I feel as though I would be a great addition to any business or company. I learn quickly and I have what it takes to succeed and possibly climb the ladder of promotion. I would love to hear back from your company and I know you will not be disappointed.

I look forward to hearing from and possibly becoming an addition to your company.

Thank you,

Esprit Hodge

## **OBJECTIVE**

I am looking to find a position that will constantly keep me busy, expand my knowledge and experience, and that will allow me to possibly progress in my chosen field. I am a hard worker and I know that being professional on and off a job is a must. I know that I have a lot to offer in any position if given the chance.

## **SUMMARY**

I currently just moved to Texas, because of family. I am able to start ASAP. I have years of experience in Customer Service and Admin experience. I have great references that are available upon request and I am very flexible with hours and overtime. I learn quickly and have experience in word, powerpoint, and excel.

## **EXPERIENCE**

## **Customer Service, IRT**

Houston, TX — 2012-2012

Answering high volume calls on a daily basis, troubleshooting phones, billing support, taking payments, bill advising

## Accomplishments

- Recognized for low Average Call times
- Recognized for low wrap-up times and low hold times
- Rewarded for outstanding Customer Service

## **Customer Service/ Admin, Curphey and Badger Law**

Tampa, FL— 2011-2012

Deed Specialist, Answered phones, setup board meetings, corrected and made new deeds according to state guidelines and regulations. Made deeds surrounding: marriage, divorce, death, and custody. Dealt with lawyers on a daily basis face to face, via email and over the phone

#### Accomplishments

- Recognized for making all deadlines in a timely and orderly fashion
- Provided outstanding customer service

# Family Worker, Head Start

Tampa, FL — 2010-2012

Family caseworker for parents and students. Worked with parents on saving plans and community assistance, family resolution, safety plans, and career outlooks.

## Accomplishments

- Recognized as Star Caseworker of the month
- Resolved cases in a timely and orderly manner
- Helped Parents come up with healthy organized plans

# **Admin, Spears and Spears Property Management**

Portland.Or — 2005-2010

Worked with high volume of calls, handled making and setting appointments, maintained word and excel information, set up board meetings, helped with new hires, training new hires, maintained all office work, some payroll, filing, faxing, and scanning.

## Intern/Admin, Stahancyk, Gearing, Rackner and Kent Law

Portland.Or — 2003-2005

Worked with high volume of calls, handled making and setting appointments, maintained word and excel information, set up board meetings, filing, faxing, and scanning, delivering information to and from other Law firms

## **EDUCATION**

## **Portland Community College, AAS**

Portland. OR — 2008-2010

Major- Psychology, Currently enrolled in Kaplan University Online for Paralegal Degree

#### Central Catholic High School, Diploma

Portland, OR — 2000-2004

One of the many Portland, Or Private College Prep Schools, I graduated in 2004.  SKILLS  Honors English A/P Science Volunteered way over the required minimum hours: Providence Care Center, KASA for kids and International House of Spanish
REFERENCES Available upon request.